Austria
Marist College
Austria
1789 1984
Marist Archives and Special Collections 3399 North Road, Poughkeepsie, New York 12601
Lowell Thomas
2.1.1.1.1
1203 linear feet
Items in this collection do not circulate and may be used in-house only.
Austria
- Lowell Thomas Papers
  - Graphic Materials, 2
    - Photographs, 2.1
      - Glass Plate Negatives, 2.1.1
        - Frank R. Roberson, 2.1.1.1
          - Austria, 2.1.1.1.1
              - The old fortress, Kufstein, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 1 (Box 1173)
                5x7
              - Old fortress on a rock, Kufstein, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 2
              - The valley of the Inn, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 3
              - Narrow street, Hall, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 4
              - Street in Hall, Ehn Valley, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 5
              - Marie-Thereseien Strasse, looking toward the Anna Saule, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 6
              - Marie-Theresein Strasse showing style of architecture, Innsbruck, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 7
              - Looking down Marie-Theresien Strasse toward the mountain, Innsbruck, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 8
              - Looking down Herzog-Friedrich Strasse, Innsbruck, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 9
              - Golden Adler Hotel in the Herzog-Friedrich Strasse, Innsbruck, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 10
              - Golden Adler Hotel, Innsbruck, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 11
              - Balin Strasse[?] near the railway station, Innsbruck, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 12
              - Old castle just outside of Innsbruck, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 13
              - Armor of King Theodorich, Innsbruck, before 1916; 14
                4x5
              - Innsbruck von Berg Isel, Austrian Tyrol, copy, before 1916; 15
              - Innsbruck von der Weiherburg, copy, 7/1/1910; 16
              - Modern castle in the Bremer Pass, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 17
              - View on road just south of Innsbruck, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 18
              - In the Val Ampezzo, Dolomites, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 19
              - Frank R. Roberson and Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson in automobile in Ampezzo Valley, Dolomites, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 20
              - The Campanile, Cortina d' Ampezzo, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 21
              - Fields of flowers, mountains, before 1916; 22
              - Garden, before 1916; 23
              - House, many pictures on wall, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 24
              - Street scene, Innsbruck, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 25
              - Men climbing, Schneerinne, copy, before 1916; 26
              - Mittenwald, copy, 7/1/1910; 27
              - Dolomitenst, copy, 7/1/1910; 28
              - Lermoos, mountains in distance, copy, 7/1/1910; 29
              - Town and mountains, Lofer, Copy, 7/1/1910; 30
              - Ornate building, Austria, Copy, before 1916; 31
              - Man, Austrian Tyrol, Copy, 7/1/1910; 32
              - Woman, Austrian Tyrol, Copy, 7/1/1910; 33
              - Andreas Hofer, Copy, 7/1/1910; 34
              - Hans Makart, Copy, 7/1/1910; 35